to the circus that escaped the asylum
where tarot cards fly and trolls get tried
you're in the pan of those baby
my father's safe the cat daddy
yeah
Psyche in the building, cards on deck
Terror spread wild like a hacker on the net
Galanor in the corner, claws out for lies
Tricks, plot and chaos with those cosmic eyes
Lola screening on the chair, Rudy got flared
Mumbles in the mix, we don't play fair
Chat blowing up like divine confessions
True bombs drop, no time for confessions
You on logic, we bandit, drama, we mend it
Panel full of chaos, but the vibes transcending
Welcome to Psych Awakens TV, it's crazy, it's loud, it's bizarre, believe me, we laugh,
we scream, we read the unseen, Father, Psych, the cat, Daddy, King of the stream.
Welcome to Psych Awakens TV, we're truth and madness, if the same T, it's a family affair,
it's dysfunction supreme.
Prophecy and cosmic mistakes, Alyssa in the chat, she a mystery queen
DJ Electra got the beat so clean, beat her with the panther, strength divine
She teams chaos with the stare and the line, we don't do fake, this trap's too real
We roast you kindly, but the love's the deal
Got minds with swords keeping gates tight, they swing truth like justice in the moon like
Gifted subs, yeah the coke keeps growing, community wild, but the energy's flowing
Welcome to Psych Awaken's TV
It's crazy, it's loud, it's bizarre, believe me
We laugh, we scream, we read the unseen
Father, psych, the cat, daddy, king of the stream
Welcome to Psych Awaken's TV
With truth and madness, if the same tea
It's a family affair, it's dysfunction supreme
You just woke up in a lucid dream
Cards flip, candles drip, shadows in the mist
Trolls, dogs live
But they cease to exist
We're half chaos, half or a cool flame
And every night's a ritual in Psyche's name
No scripts, no filters, no chilling sight
We stream raw truth to the morning light
So grab your tea, grab your mic and vibe
We the strangest family
This ain't YouTube. This is an underworlds talk show. You are now initiated.
Father Psyche is spoken. Spoken.
Hi. Wow, I'm really red today. It's oh my god, it looks like shit.
Oh my God, I'm sorry.
Not feeling great.
Not feeling 100%.
Getting like really tired.
Like a little bit upset and stuff.
But anyone that's come up, you're welcome up.
There's the link.
Kind of like, I'll be here to let people up and stuff
I don't know. Any questions? I'll address anything if anyone wants to say hi or anything as you just see like a few people here and no one's saying anything yet, so...
Thanks for being here. Remember when I used to go into the Blink it all the time.
I'm gonna try to be here. Hold on. Where's my mouse? You want to come up?
Uh, I know I'm a handful. Uh,
I'm sorry. Anyone has to put up with me. I'm like, not an easy person to
I'm sorry.
Got it throwin' shades, Ziggy puttin' on a show
Rans laughin' wild JT's
Got receipts with circus clowns
And digital seats
Midnight chats and pixel fights
Trolls and armor, neon lights
Bandhammer swing, but I still say hi
Cause chaos is love
Biggie drops a diss track, ran lights and smoke
Gotti says something deep or maybe just a joke
JT's in the corner, dropping prophecy lines
Meanwhile, I'm the priest of this circus divine
like um, Alexandra did nothing wrong. She didn't she's like she's really trying to like get to the
bottom of it and is like she's right about so many things or you know what she's bringing up. I
think she wants to do like you know me not talking about her and stuff so I'm next not going to bring
I've been through like narcissistic abuse cycles before and stuff, but it's like I am like trauma-bonded to
Beta but beta was like
I
Felt like a lot of acceptance at first and like a
Kinship
It all changed
I don't like it was it started when people started getting involved and like I could see it like on the horizon like
Eventually like they're gonna get through to her like
She'll turn against me she did beat I did
That I don't know why am I like there's something about
This it's like
It's like my fault or something
How many trouble like talking about it, so I'm not gonna try it's like oh here we go
Hi
Thank you. What's up, bro? What's up? How are you?
Good good, bro. How you been?
Like like for real man, like like let's talk man being you like what what's going on man like I
Know you're in a bit of a funk. I know you're not feeling well
You know, I know your spirits are down. You're you're you're depressing shit like that, you know
I know she's kind of like
Fucked up right now. You know, it's not
Just like a mess like I create myself and then like I
Don't know I just understand everybody that's like had enough of me I have it up myself sometimes like I understand
I don't I don't know. I'm just like but do you kind of understand what where people are coming from though?
Like as far as like we're
Well, I don't want to speak for other people. I'll just speak for myself. Yeah. No, no every
Wow, if I'm I'm a
enacting like cycles or like playing a part of it
I mean, it's like I I just wanted everyone to get along but it's like I guess like, you know, some people don't want it or like, you know
That's not part of like they just they know they won't ever get along with somebody
So that's like I'm not I can't like force people to be friends or anything
right and then it's like
Again, it's like, I want to, if I want to talk to all the people, I would hope that would be okay, but it's like, I don't know, it's like, I don't want to be.
Yeah, you don't want to be in a spot, you know, you're between a rock and a hard spot right now where you kind of have to pick, like, where you're going to go, like, which road to go on, what's the best outcome, which is the best decision to go on.
Yeah.
Mason, what's up, bro?
You guys hear me, okay? Yeah, I could hear I could hear you psyche. I can't hear Mason
Mason, are you there?
Okay, these ends I have a little mic trouble, but
Yeah, what's up Mason?
Jay dog, what's up Mason? I hear you
Hey, Jay dog, can you hear me? I could hear you, but it's coming in and out like your audios
It's coming in and out man your audio. I could barely hear what you're saying man. Oh
Mason, how are you Mason?
Okay, I'll just Mason come back in a little bit. Okay. Oh, there he is. So we're still good
Yeah, but nothing ever went wrong. So we're still good. We're good. We're good Mason. We're good
Like what happened with us?
Nothing happened with you with us. What do you mean? Like I just haven't been on lately and like you haven't been coming up and stuff
You haven't come yeah, I haven't talked to you. I know and you miss me
Yeah, I thought we'd be like hanging out on here and stuff like that. Sorry
God what's up God? Hey guys, what's up?
We're Mason go Mason. It's your favorite. Why is this guy acting like a dummy though?
He's what do you mean?
You know how he asks questions all the time. He's acting like a dummy. Why does he do that site? Why I?
Don't know. Well, I don't think he's doing that. Come on. God
Mason, why do you act like a dummy?
Mason
Oh
God my god left Mason are you there?
Okay, I think I think we lost Mason
He'll be back. Okay
Everything's good man. Everything you know what it is psyche. It's because
Do you remember what you told me like a while back? Do you remember you told me how you said you?
sometimes kind of like the
Humiliation type of thing like what the like when you're with another man like if you like you like to be spit
Like kind of like
Well, yeah, but it's like
that that plays into
the type of like the
How would you say not I'm not gonna say behavior. Yeah, I'm gonna say behavior to where you kind of like the self
the humiliation like
You like that
Humiliation rituals for like years like oh
Rituals it's like but is that something you like psyche or is that so?
I would hopefully graduate from but they just won't end like they won't like
It's like it's never like
receiving like the acceptance finally is just like constantly
You know what it is it's like it's like a dog chasing a mail truck
It's like they don't know what to do when they caught it and it's kind of like this
It's kind of like what Alexander bro. I'll say it like this from my perspective what I've seen
She feels from what I've seen. She's hurt by you psyche
and i believe he's hurt by you because you took the friendship that you had with her for granted
it's kind of like this it's kind of like all that happened was all of a sudden like you know i don't
think i did anything well i'm gonna explain to you how because i saw what happened i'm gonna
explain to you as an outsider and not biased or anything like i'm not picking sides or i'm not
saying someone's right or someone's wrong or nothing like that i'm just telling you like from
What I had seen is it's kind of like this. It's like you got a new girlfriend. Let's say let's just say like this
Hypothetically, you're a straight man
Your ex girlfriend was beta
Okay, you and beta broke up. You guys have a bad tumultuous fucking foul breakup
then you met Alexandra
Alexandra would be the new girlfriend and
You know, she treated you nothing but what kindness gave you everything of her
You know everything she could have be of herself everything and
You all you did was just talk about
the ex-girlfriend which was beta beta beta it's kind of like
You're kind of spitting in the face of the new girlfriend
You know what who's right there with you by a key car or mentioning the old one?
Okay, be it was a bit of be it was kind of a focus of hers too though, and it's like
I mean, I would have been have j-doll. Can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you Mason
So I saw you what's
I don't know if actually, you know if that's what went on on your guys's end because I don't know what what you guys talk
About behind the scenes psyche. That's your guys's business
but from what I've seen on the outside, that's what it looks like to me and
Alexander loves you, bro. I know I know she loves you
She thinks you're like the coolest ever and I think you're the coolest ever bro
She we she wants to continue to be your friend. That's just she's putting just in between you guys
Just so she don't get hurt because it's kind of hurtful when you're constantly bringing up the arch nemesis
Which is aka beta
All the time saying all I want to do is be friends with this person again
And just bring her back in and it's kind of like well, and it's an Alexander's case. It's kind of like okay. Well
You know that she made a get thread against me. You know this this is and how can you want me to fit at the same table?
We're not like I never dated beta
I know, I know, it's all hypothetical.
It's all like hypothetical.
It's all like fake, like.
I just don't feel like, I mean, it's like,
it's all been friendships.
And I think that I just have a bad time with friendship.
I just like our relationships in general.
I'm not very good at it.
Like I've always been like kind of like a lone wolf.
And then so it's like, I can get dragged into social dynamics.
Prepared for because I just don't understand or maybe they're just like, you know subconscious stuff like like working out
Oh, I have some reading
But it's like I didn't want to hurt anybody and it's like like I just wanted everyone to
Like that's why even if I have a sense of humor about things or like I'm like try to be like
Funny or something or like like light in the mood. It's just I always like
Try to like
It was kind of like this it's kind of like
Alexander's friendship wasn't good enough for you. You still want to beat us, you still want to beat us, and beat us like the old terrible goal.
Why is it like one or the other? I don't understand like why it's one or the other with them.
Well, let's get this. Alexander didn't make it that way. Bita put it that way. Just the same way how Bita puts you in the same position with me and you.
When she tried to make you choose, either same thing with clumsy.
Betta's the one who made this ultimatum. She's the one who put the head out on Alexandra
She's the one who made the get threat. She's the beat of the one who get all this shit
She's the one who made made a line. Nobody made any mind. Betta made the line
And yeah
Well, yeah, but it don't have to be complicated like I told you psychic it don't have to be complicated if you truly like I said
You and beta and you guys do make a good team. I'm not gonna lie and say you guys don't you and be the you guys are like the yin and yang
Like you guys are like a two Lego pieces that you guys just snap together
But at the same time you guys are oil and water
You know as you guys are not mixing and beta wants to try to control your your narrative
She wants to control you as a person
Which is not cool, but if you want if that's something you're okay with psyche
She wants to control
No, it's like I give I basically what I'm really confused about is like I did give up on be the like, you know
Basically, I'm not really in a way man because in a way
She's still getting brought up because in a way you're still longing for that that when you play it's kind of like this a scoring lover and I say if I broke up with somebody like say if I broke me and my wife got divorced.
Heaven forbid.
We got divorced and then all I'm doing is listening to old Spanish songs I'm playing old videos of her.
I'm constantly just, you know, I'm not over it.
I'm all I'm doing is just constantly, you know,
refreshing the memory.
So the best way to get over it is like the way,
you know, it's kind of like the old scene,
the best way to get over somebody is to get on somebody.
So have you heard of that saying psychic?
Like the, yeah, it's kind of like,
you got to just kind of brush over
and Alexander was supposed to be that new somebody
to bring a fresh start and to, you know,
Have everything good, but then beta put that fucking
Get thread out on her clumsy came out. Thank God for clumsy. He came out with the truth
Exposed beta's ass Carl came out exposed her Alexandra exposed her fucking I did everybody exposed her man because she's fucking crazy, man
You don't you don't need her approval psyche. You don't you have a lot of other people here
That do love you and do want what's best for you and do want you to say no and not humiliate it
Jada, what's up? What's up, Mesa?
Hey, Jada, do you actually did you actually see the chat like what they're saying like they told me to ask you why?
But I don't I don't know how to ask you why because I mean, I don't want to ask you why
Ask me why what what does it sing?
They were saying something about me trying to ask you why about something J dog. That's what I want me to ask you why I
Don't know man. They're talking shit in the chat. I ignore the chat one especially if I'm on panel
I really ignore the chat unless it's you know something psyche or somebody else the host brings up
But I really ignore him cuz I'm up. I'm really trying to have like the most serious conversation with psyche because I
Really want psyche can know like if you really
Yeah, we're still cool though, right like we're still cool. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, absolutely man. We're we never stopped being cool
We've always been cool
We we want to be sure because I haven't talked to you like in a while Jade dog
It's been a while like you know since we've got back to each other
So I got back to you or we got back to each other. Yeah. Yeah, man
Well, we've been busy man and psyche, you know, he's been streaming off and on you know different times and stuff
Well, but I'm glad we got able to hang out right here. No, here we are Jade. Jada
Be honest with you haven't came back to psyche's a panel of like in a long time. I haven't been here like for a long time
Yeah, well, I'm glad you're back man. I'm really glad and I know psyche's glad you're back to me and a lot of people are glad you're back
Okay
Yeah, yeah, like yeah
But I'll just say this I'll say this if you truly do love beta and I know I know you love beta man
I know you do and it's okay. I know you love beta and beta loves you
Beta does love you. I said like
You make a friendship man, like I said, I love you psyche as a friend and as a my homeboy I
Don't need them to get I have friends that are enemies
So I don't I know but but here but this is the issue man
We can't all get along and the reason why is because of stuff that beta has done
To other parties. She doesn't want me in the psyche verse. You don't understand psyche
So in order for you and her to be friends J-Dog has to step away and and you know leave the psyche verse
And if that's what you want psyche, I will do that for you
If you do want beta that badly, I will walk away. I won't talk shit on you
I mean, I don't like beta is like an idea at this point. It's like because she's not who I
Fell in love with or like liked or whatever. She's like, well, yeah, it was a fake man
It was a it was a pretend person
You know what you fell in love with the image of what you thought she was
Back like if you look at like the rap like, you know, this is like she's acting like this is this rapping or whatever
It's about bronze bird
Listen, it's like
Thank you
Sike
But cat lady is calling for you, man. I got a fucking job Mike. This bitch is fucking making me irate
Fuck you at man. I will go dyke if I stay on the panel for another motherfucking minute
Got shit to do
Yo, shout out to chat. Yo, and let me tell y'all saying
Bronsburg doesn't know how to fucking be lit. I'm always lit. He's quitting you son whether they don't win
When wait, you know white person and this guy's black
And she did a good job at fucking China battle with this like guy with a bird emoji
And she took the W. Yeah
You lost though. I did I
Don't know that's like one example
The only thing about a beetle man, let me just tell you, you pick the beetle door, it's going to constantly be this over and over and over again.
Beta is a type of girl where she likes to fight with somebody.
Make you feel like you're the problem and want to be chased over and over and over and over and over again
It's like a abusive
Shove it down your fucking throat one by one when you dox your fucking wife
You came up here and you fronted your own fucking wife. You fucking ice cream chucker hot dog fucking
Splendor learn
Yeah
You know J-Doc literally like was like this is my ex-wife
He came up here, and he showed his fucking wife. I would never fucking front about my exes. No
She does it all the time
Yeah, we keep on laughing or why are you mad about it?
Then I'm mad because she should not be in here. I'm not gonna come up here with a picture of my ex cuz
My ex is cute too, I wouldn't be up here like oh here's my ex
Look look this dog J dog went from like writing from groovy Jimmy
He was groovy Jimmy's bride and I let me give you a little history
Who bought fucking groovy Jimmy to my fucking panel? It was J dog. He said
He I know you want me to be groovy Jimmy? He brought him over there. I have no hate for Jimmy
But it was Jay dog once Jay dog got so-called Docs. He was such a pussy him. He bent over backwards
Psyche what's up? Hold on. We're through this group. It's not safe. It's not me. It's sorry. Can you hear me?
Yeah
What's up here
Here's a boyfriend right there
I'm actually about to start alive myself
It's good
You're gonna be featured in the stream. It's gonna be fun
Have fun with this.
Sorry, girl, go ahead.
I didn't, again, I didn't.
Have fun, girl.
Make me famous.
Don't worry.
All right.
So G-Dog is what we call a homosexual.
a lot of this guy called you a faggot, just called you a faggot.
You are a big homosexual, RG, like your father was before.
You're called a homosexual who paid groupie Jimmy for $500,
and after he rejected you, you started harassing him.
That's what happened. And then you started harassing him, girl.
Then you started harassing your buddy and friend. That's what you did.
Hold on to all that work, Jimmy. That's exactly what the hell you did, RG.
What you found out groupie Jimmy was a psycho, then you wanted to be friends with him.
I thought you did, RG.
Isn't that weird?
You harass people who are mentally ill. You go,
I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk, I'm not gonna let you talk
There's an item. Are you done?
What's up, Mason, right? Well, I have a question for you. Was that a crow? Was that a crow earlier like a picture of a crow?
Hey Mason, are you not close actually?
You used to be quite common collectives. You used to own the trolls and now you're on finals burger like 24 seven
Something happened
What happened?
What I wouldn't mean what happened?
Why are you sparing it all the time? You used to be cool
Nothing about me, you know nothing
You are a homosexual, a guy right there with the hands on his face, he's hiding himself.
I just dropped a link to my stream that's coming up in a few minutes.
It's J-Dog, I know you love attention, you're going to be featured in it.
Congratulations.
Yes, what are you going to do?
You can be in my stream that's about this story.
That's all you can do is dogs can't do anything.
Show up to my door.
There might be some of that.
I don't care dog. I'm already dogs. What can you do?
What can you do?
I just want to know why he's not so crazy.
You can't do anything.
This is awful, mate.
Nothing.
This is all he does, though.
Go up to my door.
I would love for either RG or...
Oh, wait a minute.
Walk and blow me up.
I'm going crazy.
Go up at my front door.
Show up at my door knock I would more than half our lives came to shit out of me
Walking yesterday out of breath panting
Yeah, because I'm drunk I'm a fat fuck I can't do this like I did when I was in my 20s is exactly
I cannot I'm double
You're right there behind me
You wouldn't you wouldn't do shit
I would love for you to come. I would love for you to come. Yeah, that's why I carry weapons
You don't fuck. I don't fight who fights. You're also an admitted felon
Who fights these days
Who doesn't know I carry a weapon and I carry knives on me. I carry a lot of stuff on me.
Come and try these are you know what to you motherfuckers come on
RG come both
I would love it come at me. Oh
Let me take couple mushrooms
Let's go at it. Oh, gee
Randall Graves talk
Yeah, that's exactly who you are. That's your moniker you stole it from that movie clerk sound just like him
I know you're not. I know you're not. Yes. Don't worry. You're not
going to say about it. You're not going to. It's okay. It's okay.
It's not me. It's not me guys. I'm not telling you. It's not
me backstage. We have dope in an ox baker. I need to make sure
that dope. No, they're porn bombers.
I got people waiting for me. I gotta go. Uh Docs J. Don. I'll
Yeah
Not even loud on Jimmy you don't fuck stupid ass motherfucker
J J dog why are they doing that stuff though, man? Why are they talking like trolls? These are my trolls
I've been fighting them for years years in years. They're gonna do a nice thing about J dogs mental health. That's why I came up
That's what they're gonna do
About me because they got nothing to do like I said come make me famous if that's what you want to do
Because I'm concerned about your mental health J-dog. That's why I came up here. There's no mental health. You stupid fuck
No, no, I'm crazy recently. I don't know what's going on. I know who you are
What happened you know, you're gonna let people talk to you like that like you're left people be that way
You know
Your motherfuckers are pieces of shit
Nobody's press
I know it's crazy chaos, huh?
Yeah, I've seen so many other people are you tell the people what the lives think about
but they can get a synopsis of this
We can tune in
You're not you know, you're not very interesting testing testing one two three
I've seen Jay dog around I never noticed this before but man he looks like schlitzie. Oh my god. It's like a dead ringer
Google gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble gobble
Motherfucker lives in the UK. Why you live in the UK, bro? You ain't even allowed to have weapons over there. You're a pussy
Call the body call them
This is what I'm talking about. He's completely right. He's completely right.
J-Doug, just ignore what he says and stuff like that.
Me and J-Doug told me they'd love to you.
No, you see that's the lies they make up. That's the lies they make up Mason. Don't believe what they say they're liars, bro
No, fuck these motherfuckers are pieces of shit. They're nobody's nobody. They think that they know everything
They don't know anything. I don't know shit
I'm running the script
But they're gonna go along
I'm straight though. I like
See the guy right there with the hands on his face, he's a homosexual for sure he's a closeted homosexual
Rg loves me
Like oh, I know I think you want to be a Mason. Oh, no Mason RG loves making love with other men
You know what? Be careful with him Mason because RG will try to make a move on you
What are you gonna do if he makes a move on you Mason? Tell me what you'll do
On you are crowed
I'll try to get away, J-Dog. I'll try to get away, man. I'll try to find a way to get out of here.
What if they grabbed you, like, physically grabbed you? What would you do, Mason?
I would grab you, J-Dog.
Well, I'm not a fighter
Scenario for Mason J doggie. It's really odd. Yeah, dude. Why are you trying to grab Mason? That's weird
Krog obviously
By the way fascination
Yeah, exactly what you would do RG you love that you love torture porn. Thank you. You ask me Jimmy
Did you do it, dog?
That was cheap.
And you take me to $600 to have sex with them,
and you turn me down.
J-dog is rightful, R.G.
I would risk my death.
Prog went along with that motherfucker, Tinky,
If I was black, I would have a better fucking voice.
I'm white and I can rap and better fucking do better verse.
You are so stupid fucking blonde bird, fucking golden girl.
I will fucking bend you over and make you fucking hell.
You're going to my show.
You must be crazy, you see?
Come on man, talk about you guys too easy.
Oh, yeah, by the way, we're going live again tonight.
We're going live tonight and we're going to talk about it.
We can't have a density.
We're going to talk about it.
I trashed you out with the motherfucking girls
so you wouldn't understand me.
I'm a king.
Why do you want to mess with me?
I know that.
Bird
Board you look mad boy when I look at your avatar when I did the zoom and matter of fact you still trash. It's like Jim
Okay, that worked okay, whoa psyche
Yes
Hey Mason, you can come stay at my house at 699 West fall blue carbon you
Stupid mother fucker J dog stupid ass mother fucker J dog
I do that motherfucker Krog fuck him that guy's a stupid motherfucker. He's docks and pieces. What was
Jada, what's going on here man? Like was that a crow or what was that about or what was that thing?
Krog is a troll from another community I come from
He trolls one of my friends gruby Jimmy. You haven't met gruby Jimmy
He trolls him. No
Anybody that's friends with him. They'll troll them and follow them to everywhere every panel they go to and that's what they did here
Those are my enemies. Yeah, but Jada, I'm just here, Jada, I'm just here to be your friend and I'm just here to report psyche
I'm not trying to uh, like start any kind of like, you know
Homosexual activity or anything like that or starting a kind of drama. Who the hell is telling you about homosexual activity? Who?
Our Archie black Archie, right? I know okay. Well if he tells you he's homosexual avoid him man
And like I told you if he comes at you, bro
Get away from him because he will come at you. Yeah, I'm just trying to avoid it. RG
I'm just trying to avoid it or avoid it. Yeah, he's a homosexual. He's a closet homosexual at that
He tried to go he tried to go with my boy groovy Jimmy and
Groovy Jimmy avoided him. He paid him six hundred dollars
And he tried to say he wanted to have sexual relations with them.
Groovy Jimmy still avoided them, told him no, blocked him and ever since then,
RG and all these other guys have been harassing my friend Jimmy and me along with Jimmy's girlfriend and other people associated with him.
That's what this is about.
That's nothing to do with D-Mation.
They're not after you.
Well, J. No, I was just coming here just to you know, just hang out and stuff
I wasn't trying to do anything like you know, I was trying to do anything wrong or anything like that. Oh, no
I know bro. Don't worry about it. Don't worry about it. I'm gonna worry about it
There's nothing for me to like worry like right
No, don't worry when they come at you just avoid them
Like I said if they come at you especially in a gay manner and they try to like grab you and shit like that just
Go the other way
Keep going the other yeah
Okay, that's that's what you're into if you're into it then you know more power to you
But if you're not like you say you're not then go the other way dog
I just try to I mean, I'm just really I don't know. I'm not really into that kind of stuff though because that's not
I'm married bro. I'm a straight married man
I don't get down that way either but psyche is gay and psyche is my friend and
I don't see anything wrong
Yeah, thank you. You're great. You're straight also, right?
Yeah, straight also. Yeah, it's me. So at least your friend. So it's okay. It's all good. It's okay
Yeah, I'm just making sure J dog that things go the things go the way they're supposed to go, you know, oh
They will bro. I mean, it's really J dog
It's really up to psyche though because this is his channel like he's the one who's supposed to decide that kind of stuff
Yeah, it's up to psyche. It's a hundred percent on psyche what he wants to do
But do you think like he's doing a good job the way he ran it?
I think he's doing a good job the way he ran everything and the way he pulled the people off and get them on and everything like that
Yeah, I think it's I think he's supposed to get rid of the ones that are just like making weird stuff happen
Yeah, yeah, but he did it quick because before
They would before they used to porn bomb, but now he knows how to do it where he's you know quick about it and pull it off and
Now he gives it real quick. He's like he's good at this. Yeah. Yeah, that's what happens
Jadon, that's what needs to happen. It's just like a psyche needs to correct correct the things that happen and just fix that
Yeah, oh man, so Mason what you up to man psyche
That's fun. Yeah, I'm just here just to chill. It was fun. Tell me it wasn't fun
Yeah, but don't worry man, I have I'm not gone nowhere and nobody's abandoning you Alexander hasn't abandoned you
I haven't abandoned you
We haven't gone nowhere. We're still your friends
Thank you. Well, we're friends man. We're never gonna stop being your friends unless you don't want us to be your friend anymore
I never like I never want to like
Choose
Anybody over like another person or make I know okay see that that's the right way to go the one who made you to make that choice was beta
Bita try to make you choose. You try to say get rid of Jay dog or you can't be friends
That's originally how some of this shit started and then she fucking put a hit on
Alexandra with clumsy trying to make plans to you know evaporate her
So
In terms of like that like in terms of like evaporating I would just watch something and set now term was used
Like the way she kind of used it like and that was like I was like whoa
Like and she's like oh, it doesn't mean anything. It just means like when you evaporate somebody
I mean, I think about like their soul like, you know drying up and like stuff like or like, you know
Just being so in a way. She wants to
Go in the essence of a person
Yeah
Well, dude, that's not true
Jadon, that's not true what Fitz sage said he says I sleep with you and stuff like that our dream about sleeping with you
None of that's true man. Who's ignore the chat bro. They're trolls. They're trolls man. Yeah, that's what it said in the chat
That's why I don't read the chat man. I avoid the chat because they're just they're trolls. They're gonna talk shit
They're gonna make up stuff. That's not true
That's
J-Dot yeah, they're speaking up
It's not even supposed to be I know or what they're saying. I know I know it's supposed to be funny, bro
They're trying to be funny. They're trying to make last
joke
It doesn't always come off funny though J-Dot because sometimes it's
Some of it is downright mean some of it is straight up fucking slander some of it is straight up trash, but
What does it know actually I gotta learn
Well, you know to decipher what what comments to really pay attention to in which one's not to yeah
That's why I didn't bother with the cat. I just I'm on the panel and I'm busy talking with the panel
I'm not I don't worry about the chat because then I get distracted with
Even Nazi tattoo I'm not too tattoo access powers. What does that mean?
Access no, it's an iron cross
Okay
Yeah, that's because I ride bikes. I ride motorcycles. So I'm
Yeah, I don't know if it's I don't think it's racist or anything. No, no, no the racist one they're talking about has a swat stick on the side of it
Okay, that's the German one. I know what you're talking about
Yeah motorcycles. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, J-Dog is actually he's I have noticed like there are like some like
Supremacy is in every race right and I think there's a racial and that's like not sometimes it's not even about race
It's like about like I don't know they they'll call people
They'll say the n-word about people that aren't you that you know, I don't I don't have to describe it
It's just like it's like I felt racist against myself not right from other white people, right? It's like something like that, right?
Okay
I think iron product me if I look it up like I don't think it will say anything
Yeah, look at all iron cross in the motorcycle culture. Look it up. It'll pull up all kinds of stuff
All kinds of stuff
It says Prussia
See well it was used
I don't know I'm getting a lot lots of Germany, but I mean I don't
I guess, you know, things are made things, you know, there's like the the swastika would actually use like in me piece, right?
Originally came from the the Native Americans. You know that? Uh-huh. Yeah
Yeah
I'm I don't have no swastikas on me. I am not
No supremacist or nothing like that strictly in kinemoto cycle culture. That's all what I am
I got that the real Nick I'm getting a lot of like it's like it's kind of like a really weird chat like I don't
I don't know it's a control is chef. Oh
Yeah, they're trolls man. There's trolls. They're trolls. Yeah
We haven't
I haven't left you. I'm not gonna leave you bro. I'm not gonna
I know but I don't want you to get to worry like I don't want you to be depressed and be like
Because people are like RG and like people are gonna come up here and they're gonna try to put what we call it in the troll community
We call it putting batteries in the back
They're gonna come and they're gonna put batteries in your back
To wind you up and just get your mind going and to fuck with your head. Let's try to say make you think
DJ dog turn on me. Why are these people telling me this?
What what do they know that I don't know? Maybe there's something that I don't they're gonna get you second-guessing yourself
Like I said, if you didn't come out of me if you didn't come out of me coming up on the panel and telling you face-to-face
Don't believe it because somebody can make up a fake clone account of me in the chat say some shit
Don't believe it unless it's really me
But I'm here for you psyche. I'm here for you, bro. Thank you J dog. Appreciate. Yeah. Yeah, I'm not going nowhere. So don't worry man
Okay
Well, thank you. I might just wrap up because I'm not feeling very well. Thank you. Thank you. Hope you feel better, man
Later Mason
I'm gonna put on some music and then it'll end
Yes
Are you glad I'm back today? Yes, I'm glad you're back. Thank you for being here. Okay
I love you. Okay. Yes. These are being my friends. You're not no homo. Okay. I'll be back guys
Yeah, you're welcome. Thank you, but yeah, I'm your friend psyche. Yeah, you are. I'll be back guys
We whispered her name in the temples of night
Golden wings glowed in the candlelight
Crowds came running just to see the flame
But envy was the price of fame
And now he stands where the echoes fall
With tarot in hand, hearing every call
From praise to venom in the same breath said
But the fire in his eyes burns gold, not red